ffoc.com 2010-05-23

# Privacy Policy - FFOC.com

Privacy Statement for www.ffoc.com

Stanima, Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: www.ffoc.com.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We use cookies to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site and for other purposes.

User information is collected at Stanima, Inc. for basic site registration; game, contest or league participation; and the purchase of premium content or services.

Our site's registration forms (used to obtain a user ID for the Stanima, Inc. site, or to sign up for premium services) require users to give us contact information (like their name, email address and zip code), and optional demographic information (like their age, etc.). We also keep track of which products and/or services (like subscriptions to Stanima, Inc.) that users may purchase. We use customer contact information from the registration form(s) to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the User when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings, either from Stamina or its partners; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis.

**Public Forums**  
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Specially-hardened operating systems that have been "patched" against known security risks are provided. Internal security staff for protection against emerging threats continually monitors these operating systems. All hardware systems are further protected by state-of-the-art firewall technology.No technology is 100% foolproof or secure, but Stanima, Inc. will make reasonable efforts to maintain the security of its user database.

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional communications from us, and from our partners, at the point of registration.

This site also gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications and to no longer receive our service.

You can send email to: sportsdesk@fanball.com  
You can send mail to the following postal address:  
PO Box 28336  
St. Louis,MO 63146-4133

**Correct/Update Account**  
This site gives users the following options for changing or modifying information previously provided.

**1.** Click on the "My Profile" link found at the top of most pages.  
**2.** Email: sportsdesk@fanball.com  
**3.** Send mail to the following postal address:  
     Stanima, Inc.  
     111756 Borman Drive  
     St. Louis, MO 63146  
**4.** Click on the Help link found at the bottom of pages.

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact 

sportsdesk@fanball.com  
Stanima, Inc.  
11756 Borman Drive  
St. Louis, MO 63146
